Gauresh Mandar Kamat

B.Tech – Computer Science and Engineering – KIT, Kolhapur

@ gaureshkamat002@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/gauresh-kamat/



EXPERIENCE

Walstar Technology, Kolhapur — Frontend Developer

February 2024 – Ongoing

Building and Designing Frontend for the website using HTML, CSS, Java Script, React and Angular. The work is to be performed on live projects and provide the frontend with a proper design required.

Rolls-Royce Power System, Pune — Data Analyst Intern

August 2023 - December 2023

For the analysis part I have worked on prediction models and effective ways of analyzing data. Also had been working on function development using HTML and python for functions. Worked on marine automation which included in the development of a UI for the display device of ships.

Educational Technology, IIT Bombay — Graphic Designer (Remote Internship)

May 2023 – October 2023

Design and build a 3D environment for educational purposes. Software used for the above are Blender-3D and Mixamo. The Aim for this project internship was to develop and enhance the experience of education by using virtual methods.

SKILLS

- Strong: Figma, Python, HTML, CSS, Blender3D, Microsoft office
- Intermediate: Unity, PHP, Power BI, Tableau, Java, C/C++, Android Studio, JavaScript
- Basic: SQL, MySQL, Canva, Ar-Vr, Uniplot, Azure Devops

EDUCATION

KIT's College of Engineering,

Kolhapur — Bachelor of Technology in Computer Science and Engineering

Jan 2021 - AUG 2024(present)CGPA - 7.77

Vivekananda College. Kolhapur

12th - APRIL 2019 - APRIL 2020 - 70%

New Model English School, Kolhapur

10th - APRIL 2017 - APRIL 2018 - 83%

ABOUT ME

4th year student at KIT Kolhapur pursuing Bachelor of Technology in Computer Science and Engineering. An avid Designer, software developer, Web developer, having knowledge of various languages and experience in various fields of projects and a 6-month experience of corporate working.

PROJECTS

Olib-Online Library

Olib an Online library was an idea of building a platform for student which will help students to share books, Notes and other study materials. The main idea was to help students gather study materials to save time.

TechStacks: HTML, CSS, JS, JQuery, php, Myphpadmin.

Chat App

Created a basic Chat App in which the user can enter his/her desired Chat room name which creates a new room if not already exists and users who enter the same chat room name chat in that room.

TechStacks: python, pip library

Basic Store Management

Created basic store management software to help small stores maintain their record on their mobile devices. This code was made for simple billing, recording and displaying available stocks.

TechStacks: c/c++

Data analyzation with data hypothesis

Performing Data Analysis on a data set of 350 student who logged their daily routine. This data set Included 5000 Data points and 53 Attributes to investigate Students punctuality, interest in studies as well as many other factors.

TechStacks: Tableau, Microsoft Excel

EXTRA CURICULAM

ACSES- Association of Computer Science and Engineering Student, Vice President

I have been working in the association for 3 years. Since I joined, we have held a lot of events such as workshop, Seminar and our Main event Pioneer.

Volunteer for Smart India Hackathon 2022, Accommodation, food and Finance Coordinator

I got an opportunity to volunteer the smart India hackathon as a coordinator which help me to meet new people across India.

e-Yantra Workshop April 2023, IIT Bombay

I got an opportunity to attend a two-day workshop of e-yantra where I meet different students from all over India and learned a lot of things.